{
    "puzzleQuestions": [
        {
            "question": "In Greek Mythology, who is the Queen of the Underworld and wife of Hades?",
            "answer": "Persephone"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which house was Harry Potter almost sorted into?",
            "answer": "Slytherin "
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the US?",
            "answer": "France"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the Robin Williams film where he dresses up as an elderly British nanny?",
            "answer": "Mrs. Doubtfire"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the rarest blood type?",
            "answer": "AB-Negative"
        },
        {
            "question": "What sport does Cristiano Ronaldo play?",
            "answer": "Soccer/football"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
            "answer": "206"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the longest river in South America?",
            "answer": "Amazon River"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the musical artist who sings the song 'Watermelon Sugar'?",
            "answer": "Harry Styles"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Na stand for on the periodic table?",
            "answer": "Sodium"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the actor who played Jack in Titanic?",
            "answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many points are a touchdown worth?",
            "answer": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which Disney movie is the villain Clayton from?",
            "answer": "Tarzan"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which ocean is the Bermuda Triangle located?",
            "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which U.S. state is known for peaches?",
            "answer": "Georgia"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the French name for Santa Claus?",
            "answer": "Pere Noel"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which fictional city is the home of Batman?",
            "answer": "Gotham City"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many feet are in a mile?",
            "answer": "5280"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the French name for Santa Claus?",
            "answer": "Pere Noel"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which planet is closest to Earth?",
            "answer": "Venus"
        },
        {
            "question": "Steve Harvey is a game show host. What’s that show called?",
            "answer": "Family Feud"
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie Ladybird takes place in which city in California?",
            "answer": "Sacramento"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the pretty woman in the 1990 film?",
            "answer": "Julia Roberts"
        },
        {
            "question": "Harry, Niall, Louis, Liam, and Zayn were in a band. What was it called?",
            "answer": "One Direction"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the author of the Harry Potter series?",
            "answer": "J.K. Rowling"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Han Solo’s ship?",
            "answer": "Millennium Falcon"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which company uses Santa Claus for their advertisements?",
            "answer": "Coca Cola"
        },
        {
            "question": "“Keep Calm and Carry On” is the slogan of which nation?",
            "answer": "Britain"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the character that Johnny Depp plays in Pirates of the Caribbean?",
            "answer": "Captain Jack Sparrow"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fe is the chemical symbol for which element?",
            "answer": "Iron"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of One Direction’s first official single in 2011?",
            "answer": "“What Makes You Beautiful”"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the Oval Office located in the White House?",
            "answer": "West Wing"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which bird is often associated with delivering babies?",
            "answer": "stork "
        },
        {
            "question": "In the Disney movie Pocahontas, she has 2 animal friends: a raccoon and a hummingbird. What is the name of the raccoon?",
            "answer": "Meeko"
        },
        {
            "question": "This place is known as the City of Brotherly Love. What is this city called?",
            "answer": "Philadelphia"
        },
        {
            "question": "What temperature (in Fahrenheit) does water freeze at?",
            "answer": "32"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the US version of The Office, what is the name of the city they live in?",
            "answer": "Scranton"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old do you have to be to enter into the drawing of the Hunger Games?",
            "answer": "12"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many players are there on a baseball team?",
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country occupies half of South America’s western coast?",
            "answer": "Chile"
        },
        {
            "question": "What group of animals is known as a “flamboyance”?",
            "answer": "Flamingo"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which musical artist is known for her song “Big Girls Don’t Cry”?",
            "answer": "Fergie"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jim Carrey stars in this 2000 Christmas movie about Whos in Whooville. What’s the movie called?",
            "answer": "How the Grinch Stole Christmas"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which U.S. state is known as “America’s Dairyland”?",
            "answer": "Wisconsin"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is hummus made from?",
            "answer": "Chickpeas"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the 1993 movie about dinosaurs?",
            "answer": "Jurassic Park"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote the classic horror book It?",
            "answer": "Stephen King"
        },
        {
            "question": "What language is the most popularly spoken worldwide?",
            "answer": "Chinese"
        },
        {
            "question": "What has a gravitational pull so strong that light cannot even escape it?",
            "answer": "black hole"
        },
        {
            "question": "What vegetable is known to help you see in the dark?",
            "answer": "Carrot"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the date of “The Devils Night”?",
            "answer": "October 30th"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gossip Girl was filmed in which neighborhood in the borough of Manhattan?",
            "answer": "Upper East Side"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the movie Good Will Hunting, what college does Skylar attend?",
            "answer": "Harvard"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the scientific name of the process where plants prepare their food?",
            "answer": "Photosynthesis"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Harriet Tubman known for?",
            "answer": "Leading slaves to freedom"
        },
        {
            "question": "What city is known as the City of Love?",
            "answer": "Paris"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which U.S. State is the largest?",
            "answer": "Alaska"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol season 1 in 2002?",
            "answer": "Kelly Clarkson "
        },
        {
            "question": "How many days are in a leap year?",
            "answer": "366"
        },
        {
            "question": "What food does Popeye like to eat?",
            "answer": "Spinach"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Shakespeare’s shortest tragedy?",
            "answer": "Macbeth"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which astrological sign’s symbol is a crab?",
            "answer": "Cancer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which band sings the popular ’80’s song “Every Breath You Take”?",
            "answer": "The Police"
        },
        {
            "question": "Quebec is a province in Canada. What language do they speak there?",
            "answer": "French"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the symbol that represents St. Patrick’s Day?",
            "answer": "4 leaf clover"
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened during the years 1939-1945?",
            "answer": "World War II"
        },
        {
            "question": "What year did Barbie come out?",
            "answer": "1959"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where in California is Disneyland located?",
            "answer": "Anaheim"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which U.S. State is known as the “Sunflower State”?",
            "answer": "Kansas"
        },
        {
            "question": "“I see dead people,” is a line from which horror film?",
            "answer": "The Sixth Sense"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who sings the song “Born in the USA”?",
            "answer": "Bruce Springsteen "
        },
        {
            "question": "Where do the Mamma Mia movies take place?",
            "answer": "Greece"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the Pixar movie Cars, Lighting McQueen ends up in Radiator Springs and befriends a tow truck. What’s that tow truck’s name?",
            "answer": "Mater"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who founded Microsoft?",
            "answer": "Bill Gates"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the world’s largest active volcano located?",
            "answer": "Hawaii"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote and published the novel The Metamorphosis?",
            "answer": "Franz Kafka"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of Harry Potter’s pet owl?",
            "answer": "Hedwig"
        },
        {
            "question": "What plant is known to help heal a sunburn?",
            "answer": "Aloe"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the 3 primary colors?",
            "answer": "Red, yellow, blue"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was Bruce Banner exposed to that turned him into the Hulk?",
            "answer": "Gamma Radiation"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first American astronaut to step foot on the moon?",
            "answer": "Neil Armstrong"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the #1 cookie in the United States?",
            "answer": "Oreo"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the names of the three fairy godmothers in Sleeping Beauty?",
            "answer": "Flora, Fauna, Merryweather"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the TV show friends, what is Joey Tribbiani’s famous line?",
            "answer": "How you doin’?"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the author who wrote The Great Gatsby?",
            "answer": "F. Scott Fitzgerald"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which band of brothers came back together in 2019?",
            "answer": "The Jonas Brothers"
        },
        {
            "question": "What flower is most gifted on Valentine’s Day?",
            "answer": "Red rose"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many planets are in our solar system? (Including Pluto!)",
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the social media platform that came out in 2003?",
            "answer": "Myspace"
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you call a geometric space with 5 sides?",
            "answer": "Pentagon"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which actor played the prince of Bel-Air?",
            "answer": "Will Smith"
        },
        {
            "question": "Steve Jobs, the CEO of Apple, is known for wearing a black ___?",
            "answer": "Turtleneck"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the movie Grease, where do Sandy and Danny meet for the first time?",
            "answer": "beach"
        },
        {
            "question": "Michael Phelps is an Olympic athlete known for this sport?",
            "answer": "Swimming"
        },
        {
            "question": "George Harrison was a member of which famous band?",
            "answer": "The Beatles"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country hosted the first Olympic Games in 1896?",
            "answer": "Greece"
        }
    ]
}